怎么样
So what do you think?
乔伊的家
Casa de Joey.
-我自己布置的  -少来了
- I decorated it myself. - Get out!
乔伊  这是...
Wow, Joey, this is....
-艺术品  -就是艺术品
- Art. - Art it is.
瞧  这是一张咖啡桌呢
Check this out! Is it a coffee table?
还是一只豹  傻傻分不清楚
Is it a panther? There's no need to decide.
好漂亮的枕头
Hey, nice pillow.
这是真的布偶皮吗
So now tell me, is this genuine Muppet skin?
妙极了  这水纹桌面真是太绝了
Hey, excellent, excellent water-table thing.
谢了  我也很喜欢  但你知道吗
Thanks, yeah. I love this but ya know what?
我看到就想尿尿
It makes me want to pee.
对  我也是  我想这是在考验自己
Yeah, me too. I think that's the challenge.
为什么钱德勒没来
How come Chandler didn't come?
因为他有件事
It's because he had a thing with the...
他有事
...with the thing.
我懂了
Right. I got it.
带我们去参观你家其它地方吧
So why don't you show us the rest of your casa?
最大的亮点  快来
The best part! Come on.
马桶挺漂亮
Nice toilet.
不  后面那个
No, no, no. Behind it.
-你这里装了电话  -没错
- You have a phone in here? - That's right.
我这里装了
I have a phone.
电话
In here.
-乔伊  答应我一件事  -说吧
- Joey, promise me something. - Yeah.
别用那个电话打给我
Never call me from that phone.
来了
Okay, here we go.
抱歉  苹果派卖完了
Honey, I'm sorry, they were all out of apple pie,
最后一片刚被人买走了
someone just got the last piece.
天啊  你们绝对不会相信的
Oh, my God! You won't believe this!
我刚刚被发现了
I have just been discovered.
等一等  我四年前就宣布你为法国领地了
Now wait a minute, I claimed you in the name of France four years ago.
总而言之
Anyway, OK,
答应我别发狂  直到我说完为止  好吗
now promise you won't like, freak out and say how great this is until I'm done, OK.
我刚刚认识了一家小唱片公司的制作人
I just met this producer of this teeny record company...
她说我的声音很清新  很特别
...who said that I have a very fresh, offbeat sound...
她要帮我录制"臭臭猫"的样带
...and she wants to do a demo of "Smelly Cat."
说了等我说完嘛
Okay, I told you not to do that yet.
她还说要帮我拍录像带
And she wants to do a video.
我还没说完
I'm not done yet, okay?
你们太激动了
God! Okay.
如果进展顺利  他们或许还会帮我做一个专辑
If that goes well, they may even want to make an album.
我说完了
I'm done now.
天呐  罗斯  如果你关心我的话
God. Ross, OK, if you care about me at all,
就把派从那男的帽子里拿出来
you will get the pie out of the man's hood.
-拿什么  -帽子里有个派  快去
- Get the what? - There's a pie in the hood. Go!
干什么
What are you doing?
对不起  我的派掉到你帽子里了
I'm sorry. My pie was in your hood.
现在我得去那个家伙的裤子上拿我的咖啡
Now I just have to get the coffee out of that guy's pants
我七点以前会回医院
...and I'll be back in the hospital by 7.
该死  罗斯  你快给我滚出来
Damn it, Ross! Get your butt out of the bathroom!
别激动  我在吹头发
Calm down. I'm blow-drying.
吹什么  你哪有头发
Blow-drying what? You have no hair.
怎么了
What's going on?
你男朋友在里面待了一个多小时
Your boyfriend has been in there for an hour!
真不敢相信  像是又住到了同一屋檐下
I can't believe it, it's like I'm living with him again.
我睡觉时他在
He's here when I go to sleep,
醒来时他也在
he's here when I wake up,
想洗澡的时候他还在
he's here when I want to use the shower,
我好像又回到十六岁了
It's like I'm sixteen all over again .
你不是十六岁  而且你们现在都是大人了
Well, you're not 16. You're both adults now.
出来  蠢货
Get out, you doofus!
或者可以比喻成  他是橡胶  你是胶水
Or, you know, he's rubber and you're glue.
该你了
All yours.
希望你清了排水孔的头发
I hope you cleaned your hair out of the drain.
住口
Shut up!
给我闭嘴
Cut it out!
我从没这样想要过你
I've never wanted you more.
怎么样  孩子们  我该打电话给他吗
So what do you say, boys? Should I call him?
俗语有云
You know what they say:
问你拖鞋一个问题
Ask your slippers a question...
你就疯了
...you're going crazy.
喂
Hello.
对不起  我今天没有过去
Listen, I'm, I'm sorry I didn't make it over there today.
没关系
That's okay.
你有事嘛
You had a thing.
对  听说你那里很棒
Yeah. I hear the place looks great.
别提了  我开心死了
Forget about it. I'm having a ball!
你那儿怎么样
How's the apartment doin'?
也很不错  一个规则空间
It's terrific. I mean, it's a regular space-...
大聚合
.. -fest!
不错
Well, great.
是啊  我只是...
Yeah, I just...
跟你打声招呼
...wanted to call and say hey.
好啊
Well OK then.
是烤箱定时器响吗
Was that the oven timer?
没错  朋友
That's right, my friend.
准时收看
It's time for...
《海滩护卫队》
...Baywatch!
你相信他们让斯蒂芬妮得皮肤癌吗
Can you believe they gave Stephanie skin cancer?
我还是不敢相信他们升她为副队长
I still can't believe they made her lieutenant!
你那么说是因为你最喜欢亚斯明·布里斯了
You're saying that because you love Yasmine Bleeth.
怎么可能会有人不爱亚斯明·布里斯
How could anyone not be in love with Yasmine Bleeth?
她们跑起来了
Hey, they're running.
瞧  这就是这出节目的精华
See, this is the brilliance of the show.
她们真应该不停地跑
I say always keep them running.
一个劲地跑
All the time running!
跑
Run!
跑啊  亚斯明  飞奔吧
Run, Yasmine! Run like the wind!
我以为你想自己一个人住
But I thought you wanted to live by yourself.
没错  我以为会很棒
I did. I thought it'd be great.
我以为我会有时间自己思考
I figured I'd have time alone with my thoughts.
但我发觉我的思想没有你们那么多
But it turns out I don't have as many thoughts as you think.
乔伊  你索性跟钱德勒说你想搬回去好了
Joey, why don't you talk to Chandler about moving back?
你认为他会答应吗
You really think he'd take me?
我们昨晚聊得很开心
We had a good talk last night...
可是我搬走时  把他伤透了
...but when I moved out, I hurt him bad.
我保证  他绝对想你搬回去的
I promise you, he would definitely want you back.
我告诉你  他绝对不可能搬回来的
I'm telling you, there's no way he's moving back.
可我们从没像昨晚聊得那么开心过
But we had one of the greatest talks we ever had last night.
就像
I mean, it was
我们刚住在一起时一样
It was like when we first started living together.
听着  我知道你现在听不进去
Look, I know you don't want to hear this right now
但我们看过他在新家的样子  他很快乐
... but we've seen him in his new place. And he's happy.
他都装潢好了
He's decorated.
听着  钱德勒  他向前走了  你也得看开
Look, Chandler, he has moved on, OK, you have to too.
你必须接受你们只是朋友这个事实
No. You're just gonna have to accept the fact that you're just friends now, OK,
你们不再是...
You're not...
室友了
... roommates anymore.
-菲比  可以试了吗  -好
- Okay, Phoebe. You ready to try one? - O.K.
臭臭猫  臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
他们喂你什么
What are they feeding you?
臭臭  臭臭  臭臭猫
Smelly, smelly, smelly Really bad smelling smelly cat
我的天
Whoa! Oh, my God!
是谁在唱
I mean, like, who was that?
你的伴唱团  在你后面  亲爱的
They're your backup singers. Behind you, hon.
我还以为她们只是在看我
I thought they were just watching me.
就像在水族馆那样
You know, like at, like at an aquarium, ya know.
臭臭猫  臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
他们喂你什么
What are they feeding you?
臭臭  臭臭  臭臭猫
Smelly, smelly, smelly Really bad smelling smelly cat
对不起
Okay, sorry.
我没感觉到
I'm just not getting...
大家都懂
...that everyone gets...
这只猫到底有多臭
... how smelly this cat actually is.
也许我们应该谈一谈
I just think that maybe if we could talk about this,
因为我必须要感觉到  你们真的很关心那只猫
... because I need to feel that you really care about the cat.
我们可以谈的
Honey, uh we, we can talk about this.
这里录音是按一分钟一百块收费的
It's just that this costs $100 a minute to be in here.
好  那只猫很臭  但你们爱它  开始
Oh OK. So, um, the cat stinks but you love it, let's go.
不  它绝对不可能是一只迅猛龙
No, there is no way he was a velociraptor.
不  托尼  你看他的头盖脊骨
No Tony, look at the cranial ridge, OK?
帝诺要是一只迅猛龙  它早吃了摩登原始人了
If Dino was a velociraptor, he'd have eaten the Flintstones.
对  对  你刚在睡觉吗
Yeah, yeah. Oh, were you takin' a nap?
是的
I was.
等等  托尼  等一下好吗   有电话打进来
Tony, can you hold on? That's the other line.
对  她在  我叫她回电话好吗
Hello. Oh yeah she's here but uh, can she call you back?
好  谢了
Okay, thanks.
打给乔安娜
Call Joanna.
她留号码了吗
Did she leave a number?
你看到我写下来了吗
Did you see me write one down?
我没有她的电话  呆瓜
I don't have her number, butt-munch.
那她会再打来的  别耍孩子脾气了
She'll call back. Don't be such a baby.
我才没有  你自己才是
I'm not a baby, you're the baby.
听着  能不烦我了吗
Look, you wanna get off my back?
你能别碍我的眼吗
You wanna get out of my face?
慢着  等一下  托尼
Wait, hold on, Tony. Hold on.
喂  你好
Hello. Hi,
对  不  她在  等一下
yeah no, she's right here. Um hold on.
托尼  我待会打给你好吗
Tony, can I call you back?
是我妹妹的男友打来的
That's my sister's boyfriend.
电话给我
Give me that.
甜心  听着  趁我还记得
Sweetie, before I forget,
我的避孕器是不是留在你那里
did l leave my diaphragm at your place?
妈
Hi, Mom.
你的宫殿怎么样
So how's the palace?
说起这事也怪有意思  我在想...
It's funny you should mention that because I was thinking....
这些箱子怎么回事
What's with the boxes?
事实上  我有个消息
Actually, I have some news.
那个乔伊还会回来拿他的麋鹿帽吗
Hey Chan, is that Joey guy gonna come by and pick up his moose hat
不然我就把它扔了
or should I toss it?
你要不自己问他吧  乔伊  这是我的新室友艾迪
Why don't you ask him yourself? Joey, this is my new roommate, Eddie.
幸会
Nice to meet you.
-彼此  -你好吗
- Likewise. - How you doing?
那我带走了
I'll take that.
我就是回来拿这个的
It's what I came for.
他是你新朋友啊  哪里认识的
So, this is new. Where'd you two meet?
我们在超市的民族食品区
At the supermarket in the ethnic food section.
我帮他挑西班牙香肠
I helped him pick out a chorizo.
我们开始聊
Well you know, we got to talking and uh,
他说要找地方住  而我又刚好有间空房
he said he needed a place and I had a spare room.
那里成空房了
Now it's a spare room?
是啊  那房间没有人用
Well, yeah. In that it's not being used...
我就把它空出来了
...and I have it to spare.
我拿到我要的了
Well, I got what I came for.
回见了
I'll uh, I'll see you guys.
乔伊
Hey, Joe.
你什么时候开始给头发"做造型"了
When'd you start using moose in your hair?
他是不是很棒
Is this guy great, or what?
是  没错
Yeah, he is.
真不敢相信他有新室友了  是谁啊
I can't believe he has a new roommate. Who is this guy?
艾迪什么的  他们刚认识
Uh, Eddie something. He just met him.
不会长久的  他只是填补空窗期的
It'll never last. He's just a rebound roommate.
看这个  看这个
Check it out! Check it out!
是"臭臭猫"的录像带
It's "Smelly Cat," the video!
我自己都还没看呢  如果你们不喜欢
Now, I haven't seen it yet, so if you don't like it...
那又怎么样   你们又没拍过录像带
...so what? None of you ever made a video.
滚出去  你这臭猫
Get out of here, cat! You stink!
美呆了
Smoking!
快看我
Look at me!
臭臭猫  臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
他们喂你什么
What are they feeding you?
臭臭猫  臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
错不在你
It's not your fault
臭臭  臭臭  臭臭猫
Smelly, smelly, smelly Really bad smelling smelly cat
错不在你
It's not your fault
臭臭猫  臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
-我的天  -我知道
- Oh, my God! - I know.
我的声音好美
I sound amazing!
他们不带你去看兽医
They won't take you to the vet
你显然不是他们的最爱
You're obviously not their favorite pet
臭臭猫  臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
错不在你
It's not your fault
-不  -我从没听过自己唱的歌
- Oh, no. - I've never heard myself sing before.
除了在我的脑袋里面
I mean, except in my own head.
这太酷了  我可以听到你们听到的了
This is so cool! Now I can hear what you hear!
差别很大吧
Pretty different, huh?
不要介意  我实在才华洋溢
I am sorry, but I'm incredibly talented!
臭臭猫  臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
错不在你
It's not your fault
乔伊  你好啊
Hi Joey, what's goin' on man?
艾迪
Eddie.
-早  -早
- Morning. - Morning.
我过来拿我的信
I just came by to pick up my mail.
-信在哪里  -在那边桌上
- Where's the mail? - Oh it's uh, over there on the table.
以前不都是放在这张桌上的吗
You don't keep it over here on this table any more?
没办法  艾迪喜欢把信放在那边
No, Eddie likes to keep it over there.
好了  请用吧  朋友  这是艾迪秘制鸡蛋
All right, here you go, my friend. Eggs a la Eddie.
真不错
That's great.
怎么了
What?
我还以为你喜欢
No I just uh, thought you liked your eggs
面包挖一个洞  中间放蛋  我做的那种
...with the bread with the hole in the middle, a la me!
我是喜欢  但艾迪是这样做的
I do, but Eddie makes them this way.
还真的是蛮好吃的
They're pretty darn good.
两位
Well, you guys...
我要出去了
... I'm out of here.
-再见  兄弟们  -再见
- See you, pals. - See you.
-你们处得怎么样   -再开心也不过了
- So how are you two getting along? - I couldn't be happier.
很好
Great.
我替你高兴
I'm happy for you.
好吧  够了
All right, that's it!
那个人就这样进来  新蛋先生
He just comes in here, Mr. Johnny New Eggs...
把信都挪换了地方
...with his moving the mail
还有"再见  兄弟们"
and his "See you, pals."
现在果汁也没有了
And now there's no juice!
需要果汁跟要果汁的人没得喝
There's no juice for the people who need the juice and want the juice.
我需要果汁
I need the juice!
那边还有一盒果汁
There's another carton right over there.
不止是果汁这么简单了  好吗
This isn't about juice anymore, all right, man?
好
All right.
那是什么事
So what's it about?
蛋
Eggs!
你比较喜欢谁的蛋   他的还是我的
Whose eggs do you like better, his or mine?
-我两个一样喜欢  -少来了
- Well, I like both eggs equally. - Oh, come on!
没人对两种不同的蛋一样喜欢
Nobody likes two different kinds of eggs equally.
我知道你更喜欢哪一种
You like one better than the other and I wanna know which.
那有什么差别呢  你的蛋已经不在这个地方了
What's the difference? Your eggs aren't here anymore, are they?
你已经带着你的蛋走了
You took your eggs and you left!
你就真以为我不会找到新蛋吗
Did you expect me to never find new eggs?
我要看《娱乐今宵》
I wanna watch Entertainment Tonight.
得了吧  今晚看《塞伦盖蒂平原的掠食者》
Tough noogies, we're watching Predators of the Serengetti.
别吵了
Would you guys stop!
这是我的电视
It's my TV!
-你住手  -你咬我呀
- Quit it! - Bite me!
天呐
Oh my God.
摩妮卡一直在转台
Monica keeps changing the channel.
你可真行  你去跟妈咪打个小报告啊
That's great. Why don't you tell Mommy on me?
现在我扮演你们的妈咪了
Now I'm Mommy in this little play?
好  听着  我拒绝卷入
Look, I refuse to get sucked into...
这一类畸型的盖勒家庭纠纷
...this weird little Geller dimension thing, okay?
我现在要去好好泡个热腾腾的泡泡浴
So I'm gonna go take a nice long hot bubble bath...
因为妈咪快要被你们逼疯了
...because you kids are driving me crazy!
这件事我们怎么解决
OK, what're we gonna do about this?
我们可以把《娱乐今宵》录下来
Well, I guess we could tape Entertainment Tonight.
不是说节目
Not that!
是我们的事
This! Us!
天啊  罗斯  你真是...
Oh, my God, Ross, it's.... You're just....
从你到这儿开始  我都快要被你逼疯了
Since you've been here, you're driving me....
摩妮卡  你又开始高八度了
Mon, you've gone ultrasonic again, all right?
我受不了
I just can't stand you being here...
你老是在这里
...all the time!
为什么  你为什么受不了呢
Why? Why can't you stand me being here?
我们只是在闹着玩而已
We're just having fun.
闹着玩  这叫好玩吗
Fun? You think this is fun?
是啊  我以为我们只是在闹  就像小时候一样
Yeah, come on, I thought we were fooling around, like when we were kids.
罗斯  小时候我恨你
I hated you when we were kids!
小时候你恨我
You hated me when we were kids?
对  我恨你
Yes. I hated you.
我爱你  仅仅是因为你是我亲哥
I loved you in a you're-my-brother- so-l-have-to way...
但从根本上讲  我恨透你了
... but basically, I hated your guts.
你为什么要恨我
Why did you hate me?
因为你对我太刻薄了
Because you were mean to me...
你嘲弄我  还总是横行霸道
...and you teased me and you always got your way.
你觉得那不好玩
That wasn't fun for you?
真不敢相信你恨过我
I can't believe you hated me.
可现在我爱你
But now I love you.
不只是因为我们有血缘关系
And not just because I have to.
-真的吗  -对
- Really? - Yeah.
但你现在别再惹我了
You're just gonna have to stop pissing me off.
可以
I can do that.
那我就用不着杀你了
Then I won't have to kill you.
你要看《娱乐今宵》吗
So you wanna watch Entertainment Tonight?.
谢了
Thanks.
-这样吧  -怎样
- You know what? - What?
如果你真的想看那个节目  也可以
If you really wanna watch that Serengeti thing, we can.
好吧
O.K.
听着  你们绝对不会相信的
Listen, you are not going to believe this...
那卷录像带上的歌声不是我的
...but that is not me singing on the video.
-不是吧  -是真的
- No. - Yes.
你怎么发现的
How did you find out?
唱片公司送了一张纸条来  叫我签名  要我同意
O.K. The record company sent over this paper for me to sign saying it's okay...
他们找别人代唱  这是第一条线索
...for someone else to sing for me. That was my first clue.
那你打算怎么办
So what will you do?
我没办法跟这种人共事
I can't work with people who would do this.
当然
Sure.
这个可怜的女人
I mean, this poor woman.
什么女人
What woman?
那个代唱的女人
The voice woman.
她的声音很不错  可是她没能拍录像带
She has a great voice, but she doesn't have a video.
菲比  那你呢
Okay, Pheebs, but what about you?
我拍了  所以你们得注意我
Well I have a video, you have to pay attention.
这个代唱的人她很有才华
This voice woman, she's so talented.
可是那些制片人说
But according to the producer people,
她长得不怎么样
they said she doesn't have like the right look or something, ya know.
她就像那种动物收容所里面的动物
I mean, it's like, she's like one of those animals at the pound
没有人要  就因为她长得不够漂亮而已
...who nobody wants because they're not  pretty enough or you know.
或者是像只老狗  浑身发臭
Like, like some old dog who's just kind of like stinky and.
我的天  它就是"臭臭猫"
Oh, my God! She's "smelly cat"!
那首歌真是有深度
That song has so many levels.
艾迪
Hey, Eddie.
来玩桌上足球吧
You wanna play some foosball?
不  谢了  老兄  我不太喜欢运动
No, thanks, man. I'm not really into sports.
那好吧
Yeah, okay. All right.
没关系  《海滩护卫队》要开演了
Doesn't matter. Time for Baywatch!
什么
What
你喜欢看那节目
Y-, y-, you like that show?
你不喜欢吗
You don't like that show?
不  那只是一群俊男美女在海滩上跑来跑去
Wha-, n-, no. I mean it's just a bunch of pretty people runnin' around on the beach, ya know.
那才是精华所在
That's the brilliance of it.
俊男美女
The pretty people.
跑来跑去
And the running.
我要进房看书了
I'm gonna go read in my room for a little while.
好的  老兄
Okay, man.
我思念所有友人
I think of all the friends I've known
但我拨电话时
But when I dial the telephone
没人在家
No one's home
孤单寂寞
All by myself
我不想要
Don't wanna live
孤单寂寞
All by myself
一个人
Anymore
孤孤单单
All by myself
臭臭猫  臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
他们喂你什么  一起唱
What are they feeding you? Everybody!
臭臭猫  臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
错不在你
It's not your fault
-莫妮卡  -他们不带你去看兽医
- Monica. - They won't take you to the vet
钱德勒
Chandler.
你显然不是他们的最爱
You're obviously not their favorite pet
-乔伊  -你或许不是一床玫瑰
- Joey. - You may not be a bed of roses
-瑞秋  -也没有人会喜欢闻你
- Rachel. - And you're no friend To those with noses
罗斯  歌词都唱完了  抱歉
Ross, those are the only lines we have. Back to the chorus! Sorry.